nicoclub.com 2012-05-07

# NICOclub.com Privacy Policy

NICOclub.com and all affiliated sites are the property of HDS Holdings, Inc. They are independent publications and are not affiliated with or endorsed by Nissan or Infiniti.

All information is copyrighted by NICOclub, with all rights reserved. The material within may not be copied or reprinted without written permission from the owner.

NICOclub respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it. This privacy statement is to inform you of our privacy policy, practices, and the information collected online and how that information is used.

Certain non-personal information associated with normal web browsing and usage that does not identify a specific personal identity may be collected as you navigate NICOclub. Types of non-personal information may include pages visited, browser type, ip address, and cookies. NICOclub uses such information in order to determine traffic statistics and to improve the content of our Web pages.

NICOclub does NOT EVER share your information with anyone. Upon registration, we ask that you submit certain information such as your name, e-mail address, birthday, and location. This information is ONLY used to verify you as a “real” user, contact you with relevant information, and to provide a more personalized experience within our community. This information MAY be visible to someone conducting a search engine inquiry. This is fairly common for most all forums. Again, your information will not be disclosed or sold/rented/leased to anyone. 

From time to time, we may send out a newsletter or update regarding the site via email. This is infrequent (usually once or twice annually).

NICOclub may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. We do not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from our practice.

As with most free resource sites, we have advertising on the forums. To bring you offers that are of interest to Nissan enthusiasts, we have relationships with other companies that place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. This is fairly common to most websites. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us via e-mail at webmaster@nicoclub.com.

Did you like this article? If so, please help us spread the word and share it!

  * [](http://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Privacy%20Policy%20-%20http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nicoclub.com%2Fprivacy-policy%20\(via%20@sociablesite\) "Twitter")
